Guide to the Eastern Parkway Coalition records 2007.016
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 2: Plans and maps, 1973-1988; 1.5 Linear Feet in six rolled document cases, one oversize flat box, and one loose rolled item
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans, 1986 (Flat file folder 1)
    Plans for streelights, ornamentation, etc.
    The material in this folder is too fragile to be handled by researchers.
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans (1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Oversize OS-30)
  - Reconstruction of Eastern Parkway plans (2 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Bergen Street and Dean Street - Prospect Heights/Crown Heights maps, circa 1980s (Box 10)
  - Reconstruction of Vanderbilt Avenue intersection at Atlantic Avenue, from Pacific Street to approximately 150 feet north of north building line, circa 1980s (Box 11)
  - Reconstruction of Dean Street, from Flatbush Avenue to Rochester Avenue, and Bergen Street, from Flatbush Avenue to Albany Avenue, plans, circa 1980s (Box 11)